Guide to the Association of Yale Alumni Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Association of Yale Alumni records
1826-2015
RU 792
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
53.17
(74 boxes)
The records consist of correspondence, memoranda, minutes, financial reports, pamphlets and press clippings documenting the activities and operations of the Association of Yale Alumni (AYA).
AYA (Organization)
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 8-C (YRG 8-C), Records of organizations of Yale alumni
Conditions Governing Access
While this collection as a whole is available for research, parts of it may be restricted due to law, university policy or fragility. Any restricted material will be noted as such.
Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy for their personal use should consult Copying Services information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site.
Arrangement
The records are arranged as follows: I. Society of the Alumni, 1826-1911. II. Commencement Registers, 1842-1911. III. Committee for Plan on University Development, 1917-1921. IV. University Alumni Fund Association, 1875-1961. V. Reunions, 1902-1968. VI. Alumni Board, 1939-1964. VII. Founding Board of Governors of the Association of Yale Alumni, 1971-1975. VIII. Association of Yale Alumni, 1972-1977; and in subseuqent accessions
Scope and Contents
The records consist of correspondence, memoranda, minutes, financial reports, pamphlets and press clippings documenting the activities and operations of the Association of Yale Alumni (AYA)
Universities and colleges -- Alumni and alumnae; AYA (Organization); Yale University -- Alumnae and alumnae -- Societies, etc.
- Society of the Alumni, 1826-1911; Series I
  - Minutes: record book, 1826-1834 (Box 1, Folder 1-3)
  - Finances, 1827-1841
  - Constitution, 1827-1829 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1827-1841, n.d (Box 1, Folder 5-12)
  - Minutes, 1842-1911 (Box 2, Folder 13-14)
- Commencement Register, 1842-1911; Series II
  - 1842-1847 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - 1843-1851 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - 1850-1875 (Box 3, Folder 3-4)
  - 1871-1891 (Box 4, Folder 5-6)
  - 1856-1874 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - 1875-1878 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - 1892-1911 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Committee for Plan on University Development, 1917-1921; Series III
  - Minutes, 1917-1920 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Financial report, 1918-1919 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1918-1921 (Box 7, Folder 3-4)
  - Final report, 1919 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Printed material: press clippings, pamphlets, charts, 1919-1921 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- University Alumni Fund, 1875-1961; Series IV
  - Class Agent's Book, 1875 (Box 8, Folder 1-2)
  - Secretary Books, 1890-1898 (Box 8, Folder 3-4)
  - Cash Books, 1890-1907 (Box 8, Folder 5-6)
  - Alumni Association of Fairfield and vicinity, 1907-1944 (Box 9, Folder 7-8)
  - Correspondence, 1926-1930 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Selected sample material letters, advertisements, envelopes, 1931-1942 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous material: memoranda, printing and advertising, correspondence, financial statements, 1947-1948 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Annual Reports
    - 1890-1913 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - 1891-1902 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - 1914-1937 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - 1932-1941 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - 1942-1952 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Campaign Material
    - 1953-1956 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - 1954-1956 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - 1957-1959 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - 1959-1961 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Subscriptions
    - 1890-1899 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - 1900-1902 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - 1902-1903 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - 1903-1904 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - 1905-1905 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - 1905-1906 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - 1906-1907 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - 1907-1908 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - 1908-1909 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - 1909-1910 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - 1910-1911 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - 1911-1912 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Microfilm (14), 1948-1959 (Box 16)
  - Microfilm (13), 1948-1959 (Box 17)
- Reunions, 1902-1968; Series V
  - Expenses, 1902-1948 (Box 18, Folder 1-4)
  - Expenses, 1949-1953 (Box 19, Folder 5-7)
  - Photograph (3), Undated (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Association of Class Secretaries: minutes, correspondence, Model Class Constitution, 1942-1947 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Association of Class Secretaries: miscellaneous correspondence, memoranda, 1948-1950 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Harvard 25th reunion: Report to Yale Association of Class Secretaries, 1949 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Scroll idea for class reunions, 1951 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Alumni records, information for, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous class reunion material: Class 1890-1948, 1931-1944 (Box 20, Folder 14-20)
- Alumni Board, 1939-1964; Series VI
  - Corporation: general, 1939-1953 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Constitution and By-Laws, 1941-1952 (Box 21, Folder 2-3)
  - Reports of Executive Secretary to Alumni Board, 1948-1956 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Printed material, 1951-1952 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Budget, 1951-1953 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1952-1954 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1952-1956 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Enrollment and Scholarships, 1952-1960 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - O'Hearn, Charles, 1953-1956 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Alumni Magazine, 1953-1956 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Athletic Association, 1953-1956 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Budget, 1953-1954 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Admission, Board of, 1953-1956 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Alumni Admissions, Manual for, 1954-1955 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Budget, 1954-1955 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Newsletters, Department, 1954-1957 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Graduate and Professional Schools, 1955 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, 1955-1956 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Alumni House, 1955-1956 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Budget, 1955-1956 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Development Committee, University, 1956-1962 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Form letters sent out, 1956-1957 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Newsletters, Department, 1958-1961 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Minutes and correspondence, 1958-1962 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Farnham-Neighborhood House, 1960-1964 (Box 24, Folder 26-27)
  - Minutes, reports, memoranda, 1963-1964 (Box 24, Folder 28)
- Founding Board of Governors of the Association of Yale Alumni, Series VII
  - Financial: Clerical Bureau, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Association of Yale Alumni: Historical background, 1971-1975 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Addresses, Alumni information, biographies, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Annual Report, Ramsey, Gordon C., 1972 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Assembly Election: miscellaneous correspondence, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Association, meetings: verbatim proceedings, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 6-8)
  - Bates, James H.: correspondence, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Nominations: Board of Governors Walsh, John N. III 1967, Chairman, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Board meeting: first, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Board meetings: New York, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Board meetings: Los Angeles, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Board Election meeting: verbatim proceedings, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Board meeting: verbatim proceedings, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Board meeting: final, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - "Call to Election" AYA Assembly: Grimes, D.C., 1972 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Career Advisory Committees, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Committee on AYA Committees: Walsh, John N. III 1967, Chairman, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Communications Committee: Fisher, Everett, Chairman, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Corporation resolution, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Dahl Committee Report, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Defeated Candidates list, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Drafting Committee: Payne, David M. 1941, Chairman, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Election complaints, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Election of permanent Board of Governors, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Election material, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Election returns: Assembly representative, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 28-31)
  - Election follow-up: club and class officers, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Election follow-up: class secretaries, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Election follow-up: Alumni Association of Presidents, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - Election: final report, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - Engineering and Applied Science: Correspondence, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - Executive Secretary Search Committee: Fisher, Everett 1941, Chairman, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - Finance Committee: Baldridge, Malcom 1944 chairman, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - Financial: budget, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - Financial: Yale Club of New York City, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 40)
  - Formation of the Association: mail received, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 41)
  - Future of the College and the Graduate School, Report of the Committee on, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 42)
  - Grimes, Lee: report, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 43)
  - Historical material, 1971-1972 (Box 28, Folder 44)
  - Lux Et Veritas, Incorporated, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 45)
  - Major Issues Committee: Galland, Richard I. 1937, Chairman, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 46)
  - Membership Directory: revised, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 47)
  - Miscellaneous: correspondence, memoranda, 1972-1973 (Box 28, Folder 48)
  - News Releases, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 49)
  - New York City ballots, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 50)
  - Nominations, class: Assembly Representative, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 51-52)
  - Nominations, Foreign Club: Assembly Representative, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 53)
  - Nominations, Graduate and Professional School: Assembly Representative, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 54)
  - Nominations, Yale Club and Association: Assembly Representatives, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 55)
  - Nominations, Yale Club and Association (non contes regions): Assembly Representatives, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 56)
  - Petition candidate, AYA Board: Getman, Christopher, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 57)
  - Petition candidate, AYA Board: Ludman, Angeline K., 1972 (Box 29, Folder 58)
  - Petition Telegrams: West Coast, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 59)
  - Post Election, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 60)
  - Progress memos, calendars, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 61)
  - Purchasing handbook and stocklist, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 62)
  - Questionnaires: names, addresses, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 63)
  - Ramsey, Gordon C.: correspondence, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 64)
  - Reimbursements and special expenses, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 65)
  - Reference material for meetings, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 66-69)
  - Representation Committee: Castles, John W. 1943 Chairman, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 70)
  - Requests for general information (Alumni), 1972 (Box 30, Folder 71)
  - San Antonio Alumni Association, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 72)
  - Schafer, Kathleen: employment data, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 73)
  - Student Involvement, Report of the Committee on, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 74)
  - Substantive Changes in Alumni/Yale Relationships: memorandum from Don Clifford, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 75)
  - Tangible Evidence Committee: Wibur, John S. Chairman, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 76)
  - The Ethical Investor by Simon, Powers and Gunnerman, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 77)
  - Trinity Church on the Green and City of New Haven: Agreement, Chair Alumni Service, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 78)
  - University Catalogue, draft copy of, 1972-1973 (Box 30, Folder 79)
  - "What Do Alumni Think?": E. P. Davison (lacking), 1972 (Box 30, Folder 80)
  - Yale Alumni Magazine assembly announcement: poligy, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 81)
  - Yale Alumni Magazine: xerox copy photos of Board members, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 82)
  - Yale Daily News: correspondence, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 83)
- Association of Yale Alumni (AYA), 1972-1977; Series VIII
  - Activities Reports, 1972-1976 (Box 31, Folder 1-4)
  - Publications: Officers Handbook, Athletics Report, Admission, 1972-1974 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Alumni convocation: Questionnaire, programs, 1973-1975 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Tax exempt status and Yale, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Admissions Report, Correspondence, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Undergraduate Admissions, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 10)
- AYA Online course records, 1997-2005; Accession 2008-A-122
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2041
  - AllLearn, 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - CMI, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Iraq, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Online course job description, 2001-2003 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Alliance course development, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Brodhead course, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - CMI: Administration, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Alliance online instructors and moderator training, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - CMI: Shakespeare, Script to Screen, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Salovey and Borroff enhancements, 2002 February (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - CMI: Payments, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Democratic Vistas, 2002 April (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Prometheus manuals, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Online pedagogy, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - AllLearn conference call, 2003 October 30 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Alliance 2001 marketing, 2001-2003 (Box 1, Folder 16 - 17)
  - Alliance meeting
    - 2002 January 24-25 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - 2001 December 4-7 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Yale Organizational Team - Alliance, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Alliance future courses, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Alliance 2001 course development CMI (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - eBorroff e-mail cleanup, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - eCollege, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - 2001BORI papers (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - eBorroff, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - eSalovey, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Online course interest, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - eCollege (Box 1)
    - Evaluation, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Grant, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - eClaudia, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Salovey, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Borroff, 1999-2001 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Course development, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - On-line educational programs, 1997-2000 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Association of Yale Alumni E-Course Readings for The Intelligent Emotions, 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - To Hear Their Voices: Readings, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - To Hear Their Voices Guidebook, 2001 Fall (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Online Course Readings for Professor Marie Borroff's Course "To Hear Their Voices: Chaucer, Shakespeare and Frost", 2000 Spring (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Online Course Readings: The Intelligent Emotions, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - AYA Online Course, 2000BOR, "To Hear Their Voices: Chaucer, Shakespeare, and Frost" Course Materials and Evaluation (Box 1, Folder 41 - 42)
  - Borroff, Marie, "Exercise on Chaucer's Pronunciation", 2000; audiocassette (Box 2)
- Additional material, 1951-2005; 1979-1995; Accession 2015-A-030
  Restricted until January 1, 2040
  - General administrative files
    - A. Bartlett Giamatti: notes, memoranda, correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - A. Bartlett Giamatti: travel correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 2-3)
    - A. Bartlett Giamatti: speeches and press releases, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - A. Bartlett Giamatti: travel meeting, 1984 February 16 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - A. Bartlett Giamatti: draft correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - A. Bartlett Giamatti and Benno C. Schmidt: reunion schedule, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - A Process of Understanding: the Social Sciences at Yale video project, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Activities, meetings and trips, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Admissions
      - 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 10-12)
      - 1982 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - 1983 (Box 1, Folder 13a)
      - Legacies, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Alumni directors: correspondence, 1978-1981 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Alumni fellow election ballots, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Alumni fund
      - 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 17)
      - 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
    - Alumni Grandparents' Day, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Alumni in government service, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Annual reports
      - 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 21a)
      - 1988 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Army game trip, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Army unit reunion, 1984 September 21-22 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Athletic department, 1983 Fall (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Arts convocation, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Audit report, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Benno C. Schmidt press release, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Biological sciences reunion, 1987 April-December (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Budget, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Calhoun bicentennial, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Campaign, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Chron file, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Class meetings, 1987 April 25 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Counterparts, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Columbus II Colloquium, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Committee on Development and Alumni Affairs, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 1-2)
    - Committee on Honorary Degrees, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Communications Board, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Complaints, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Council for Advancement and Support of Education (CASE), 1979-1981 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Coxe Cage/tent events, 1984 October-November (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Day at Yale, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Directories, 1982-1984 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Draft correspondence: Terry Holcombe, Undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Eastern regional office: staff assistant correspondence, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Eustace D. Theodore correspondence, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 12-13)
    - Evening at Yale, 1986 February 28 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Externship descriptions, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Externship reports, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Externships
      - 1981 (Box 2, Folder 17)
      - 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 18)
      - 1983 (Box 2, Folder 19-21)
      - 1985 (Box 2, Folder 22-23)
      - 1988
        - Alcala-Bottorf (Box 3, Folder 1)
        - Bowker-Crow (Box 3, Folder 2)
        - Danahy-Frantz (Box 3, Folder 3)
        - Gajdusek-Hagle (Box 3, Folder 4)
        - Heo-Kim (Box 3, Folder 5)
        - Kim-Kwon (Box 3, Folder 6)
        - Laff-Liu (Box 3, Folder 7)
        - Lo-Muschell (Box 3, Folder 8)
        - Nathu-Rosenbaum (Box 3, Folder 9)
        - Roseman-Somersille (Box 3, Folder 10)
        - Steinberg-Velez (Box 3, Folder 11)
        - Verras-Zymelman (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Football broadcasts, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Football: Yale v. Princeton tent, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Football weekend, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Freshman schedule, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Graduate and Professional Assembly meeting, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Graduate Class of 1940: reunion (Healy, transportation), 1984 September 29 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Harvard game, 1979 November (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Harvard game, 1981 November 21 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Harvard/Yale staff conference of alumni officers, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Honorary degree committee, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Honorary degrees, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Inauguration calls, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Inaugurations: Sandy Radizeski, 1987-1989 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Investment statements re: South Africa, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Ivy League alumni directors, 1983-1988 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Mail order business-alumni, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Media conference, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Memos, 1983-1985 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Midwest office (Spinelli), 1980 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Mini-conference: continuing education, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - MIT enterprise forum, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Music groups, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Mystery weekend, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - New Haven Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Office of International Research, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Paul C. Lambert correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Philadelphia/Yale scholarship fund, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Princeton game, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Rose Project-alumni/student center, 1984-1987 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Science film project, 1984-1986 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Social science tape: SITE, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Spring class days, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Staff memos, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Student correspondence, 1981-1986 (Box 4, Folder 20-22)
    - University calendar committee, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - University Committee on the Economic Status of the Faculty: report, 1986-1988 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Video contract project, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Video tape program, 1981-1984 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Video tape project: SITE, 1983-1985 (Box 4, Folder 27-28)
    - Weekly bulletin and calendar, 1983-1986 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Word processing study, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Yale charter amendment, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Yale/Harvard general file, 1983 November 19 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Yale/Hillhouse class day, 1982 April 3 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Yale/Navy, 1988 October 1 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Yale/New Haven agreement, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Yale/Princeton game: returns from class secretaries, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Yale/Princeton game, 1982 November 13 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Alumni college abroad
    - Alaska wilderness, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Alumni travel, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Alumni travel program, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Ancients sites of Mexico, 1985 February 21-24 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Barging in France, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Civilizations of the Mediterranean, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Educational programs, 1985-1988 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Europe's great and gentle lands, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Grand Canyon, 1985 July 6-20 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Heli-exploring in the Canadian Rockies, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - History and lore of the Rhine, 1985 May 17-20 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Kenya safari, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Northern Italy and the Adriatic Sea, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Paris City College, 1985 June 9-15 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Sailing the Caribbean, 1985 March 15-23 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Sailing the French and Italian Rivieras, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Sailing the Greek islands, 1985 September 23-October 9 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Salmon River, 1985 July 21-30 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Scandinavia/British Isles, 1985 July 14-28 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Skiing in Switzerland, 1984-1988 (Box 5, Folder 20-21)
    - Theatre trip to London, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Travel abroad, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Travel planning, 1983-1985 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Western Mediterranean odyssey, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Voyage to antiquity, 1985 October 24-November 8 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Yale in Cambridge, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Yale/Hawaii football, 1985-1987 (Box 5, Folder 28-29)
    - Yale-London connection, 1983 June (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Yale seminar in Vail, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - AYA Assembly
    - Assembly XIII: university admissions, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Assembly XVIII
      - Bus tours, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 33)
      - Cultural center, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 34)
      - Economic development, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 35)
      - Education, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 36)
      - Forms, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 37)
      - Historical, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 38)
      - Housing, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 39)
      - Lipsher, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 40)
      - Medical center, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 41)
      - On Common Ground, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 42)
      - Saturday Panel, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Assembly XIX: structure of the university, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 1-3)
    - Assembly XX: Yale's collections, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 4-5)